Hello friends, you are
very welcome to the market.  Friends, in this video we will
talk about ICICI LB Quarter Four
results.  Please subscribe to the channel.  If you
like it, please like the video.  The
company has
disclosed its quarter 4 results on 15 April 2026.
If we talk about the
dividend announced by the company,
if you see, the company is going to give you a dividend of ₹7 per share,
which is going to be
70% and here you will get to see ₹10 as per the face
value.
So, ₹7% dividend is
very good news for the shareholders here from the company
ICICI LBR and
when will this dividend be given in your account,
for that friends, there is a
30 day criteria from the company
where the company is going to deposit the money of dividend in your account,
plus
whatever news is there, you will get it here,
please subscribe to the channel, so
friends, let's go to the
balance sheet of the company's quarter 4 results,
where you will see here the
quarter 4 results,
so here you can see friends, the
amount is in crores, we will talk
in crores, what is seen this year from last year, what is the
total income of the company,
so here you can see the
total income has been shown in many ways by the company, if we
talk about the total income of last year, then
here you can see that the
total income of the company was 5851 crores last
year, this time the income of the company has increased to
6618 crores and  If we talk about last year and the
last quarter, the
total income of the company is
seen to be around Rs 610 crore.  So here we see the company
's income increasing year on year and quarter to
quarter.
Which
shows the profitability of the company.  Plus here it
shows the work of the company.  How the
company is seen doing good work.
Talking about expenses,
how are the total expenses behaving?
Expenses can be seen in many ways.  Friends, the
expenses of the company last year were
around Rs 5435 crore.  This
time the company's expenses are
around Rs 672 crore.  And these were
expenses of around ₹630 crore in the last quarter.
Here, year on year and quarter to
quarter expenses are also increasing in the same manner as the
company's income is increasing.  Let us
talk about
how much profit the company is seeing here.
Talk about after tax expenses where
how much profit the company is making after deduction of pay tax.  So
friends, what is the profit of the company after tax as compared to last
year and this year?  So
here you can see the net profit
for the period after tax.  So here you
can see that last year there was a profit of Rs 59 crore
and this time the profit of the company is
seen going up to Rs 546 crore.
But if we
look at something important here, this time the profit of the company seems to be
less than the previous quarter.
Because
in the last quarter the company's profit was around Rs 658 crore.
This time 546 crores are being seen.
So here the
fundamentals of the company changed.
Considering the expenses of the company, the profit earned by the company
this time is higher than the previous quarter.  But if we
look here, the company's profit seems to be
better than last year.
Friends, let's talk
about the EPS of the company here, so what is the difference between the EPS last year and
this year?  So
look at the EPS friends, it was here last year
with 10 points.  This time it is around 10.9 here.
Whereas in the last quarter it was
with 3 points, it was with 13 points.
So here the point ah EPS of the company is
seen increasing year on year.  It is
seen decreasing quarter to quarter.  So here the company
works a little at its level where the
company should increase its profits.
Plus you should reduce your expenses here.
Attention should be paid to taxes
so that the company makes profit.  So here the
company's expenses were
seen to be higher than the previous quarter of last year.  Plus, the
company's expenses are also much higher
here.  Thank you.  Will like and
subscribe.